questionList = questionList.concat([
	//Present
	{question:"The boy eats.", answers:["El niño come."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El niño come.", answers:["The boy eats.", "The child eats."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It is an apple.", answers:["Es una manzana."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Es una manzana.", answers:["It is an apple.", "It's an apple."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Es una mujer.", answers:["It is a woman.", "She is a woman.", "It's a woman.", "She's a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It is a woman.", answers:["Es una mujer.", "Ella es una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ella es una mujer.", answers:["She is a woman.", "She's a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"She is a woman.", answers:["Es una mujer.", "Ella es una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted es una niña.", answers:["You are a girl.", "You are a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú eres una niña.", answers:["You are a girl.", "You are a child.", "You're a girl.", "You're a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Eres una niña.", answers:["You are a girl.", "You are a child.", "You're a girl.", "You're a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You are a child.", answers:["Usted es una niña.", "Tú eres una niña.", "Eres una niña.", "Usted es un niño.", "Tú eres un niño.", "Eres un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You are a girl.", answers:["Usted es una niña.", "Tú eres una niña.", "Eres una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It is a girl.", answers:["Es una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It is a child.", answers:["Es una niña.", "Es un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Es una niña.", answers:["It is a child.", "It is a girl.", "It's a child.", "It's a girl.", "She is a child.", "She is a girl.", "She's a child.", "She's a girl."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Usted es un niño.", answers:["You are a boy.", "You are a child.", "You're a boy.", "You're a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú eres un niño.", answers:["You are a boy.", "You are a child.", "You're a boy.", "You're a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Eres un niño.", answers:["You are a boy.", "You are a child.", "You're a boy.", "You're a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You are a boy.", answers:["Usted es un niño.", "Tú eres un niño.", "Eres un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It is a boy.", answers:["Es un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Es un niño.", answers:["It is a child.", "It is a boy.", "It's a child.", "It's a boy.", "He is a child.", "He is a boy.", "He's a child.", "He's a boy."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Es un hombre.", answers:["It is a man.", "It's a man.", "He is a man.", "He's a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It is a man.", answers:["Es un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Él es un hombre.", answers:["He is a man.", "He's a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"He is a man.", answers:["Es un hombre.", "Él es un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El hombre come.", answers:["The man eats."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The man eats.", answers:["El hombre come."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú bebes agua.", answers:["You drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Yo como.", answers:["I eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I eat.", answers:["Como.","Yo como."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Un niño bebe.", answers:["A boy drinks.","A child drinks."], language:"English"},
	{question:"A boy drinks.", answers:["Un niño bebe."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo bebo.", answers:["I drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I drink.", answers:["Yo bebo.", "Bebo."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú comes.", answers:["You eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You eat.", answers:["Tú comes.", "Comes.", "Usted come."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Es pan.", answers:["It's bread.", "It is bread."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It is bread.", answers:["Es pan."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Es agua.", answers:["It's water.", "It is water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It is water.", answers:["Es agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You are men.", answers:["Ustedes son hombres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes son hombres.", answers:["You are men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Somos hombres.", answers:["We are men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We are men.", answers:["Somos hombres.", "Nosotros somos hombres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Somos mujeres.", answers:["We are women."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We are women.", answers:["Somos mujeres.", "Nosotras somos mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebemos leche.", answers:["We drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebemos leche.", answers:["We drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We drink milk.", answers:["Bebemos leche.", "Nosotros bebemos leche.", "Nosotras bebemos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebemos agua.", answers:["We drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebemos agua.", answers:["We drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We drink water.", answers:["Bebemos agua.", "Nosotros bebemos agua.", "Nosotras bebemos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You are women.", answers:["Ustedes son mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes son mujeres.", answers:["You are women."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotras somos niñas.", answers:["We are girls.","We are children."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We are girls.", answers:["Nosotras somos niñas.","Somos niñas."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas son niñas.", answers:["They are girls.","They are children."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They are girls.", answers:["Ellas son niñas.","Son niñas."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You drink water.", answers:["Tú bebes agua.", "Bebes agua.", "Usted bebe agua.", "Ustedes beben agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ustedes beben agua.", answers:["You drink water."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ellas son mujeres.", answers:["They are women."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They are women.", answers:["Ellas son mujeres.", "Son mujeres."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Ellos son hombres.", answers:["They are men."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They are men.", answers:["Ellos son hombres.", "Son hombres."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You drink milk.", answers:["Tú bebes leche.","Bebes leche.","Usted bebe leche.","Ustedes beben leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotros somos niños.", answers:["We are boys.","We are children."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We are boys.", answers:["Nosotros somos niños.","Somos niños."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They drink.", answers:["Beben.","Ellos beben.","Ellas beben."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos beben.", answers:["They drink."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Las niñas beben agua.", answers:["The girls drink water.","The children drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls drink water.", answers:["Las niñas beben agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Los niños beben agua.", answers:["The boys drink water.","The children drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boys drink water.", answers:["Los niños beben agua."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Tú escribes un libro.", answers:["You write a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You write a book.", answers:["Tú escribes un libro.","Escribes un libro.","Usted escribe un libro.","Ustedes escriben un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Usted escribe un libro.", answers:["You write a book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo escribo una carta.", answers:["I write a letter."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"I write a letter.", answers:["Yo escribo una carta.","Escribo una carta."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Nosotros escribimos un libro.", answers:["We write a book.","We wrote a book."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"We write a book.", answers:["Nosotros escribimos un libro.","Nosotras escribimos un libro.","Escribimos un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Ellas beben vino.", answers:["They drink wine."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"They drink wine.", answers:["Ellas beben vino.","Ellos beben vino.","Beben vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"I drink wine.", answers:["Yo bebo vino.","Bebo vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Yo bebo vino.", answers:["I drink wine."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Tú lees el libro.", answers:["You read the book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You read the book. (present tense)", answers:["Tú lees el libro.","Lees el libro.","Usted lee el libro.","Ustedes leen el libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Las niñas escriben.", answers:["The girls write.","The children write."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls write.", answers:["Las niñas escriben."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ella es una persona.", answers:["She is a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"She is a person.", answers:["Ella es una persona.","Es una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo leo.", answers:["I read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I read. (present tense)", answers:["Yo leo.","Leo."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El niño lee.", answers:["The boy reads.","The child reads."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy reads.", answers:["El niño lee."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Él es una persona.", answers:["He is a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"He is a person.", answers:["Él es una persona.","Es una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotros leemos un diario.", answers:["We read a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We read a newspaper. (present tense)", answers:["Nosotros leemos un diario.","Nosotras leemos un diario.","Leemos un diario."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas leen.", answers:["They read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They read. (present tense)", answers:["Ellas leen.","Ellos leen.","Leen."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos leen un libro.", answers:["They read a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They read a book. (present tense)", answers:["Ellas leen un libro.","Ellos leen un libro.","Leen un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotras comemos arroz.", answers:["We eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros comemos arroz.", answers:["We eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We eat rice.", answers:["Nosotras comemos arroz.","Nosotros comemos arroz.","Comemos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo cocino pescado.", answers:["I cook fish."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I cook fish.", answers:["Yo cocino pescado.","Cocino pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos no comen nada.", answers:["They do not eat anything.","They don't eat anything."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They do not eat anything.", answers:["Ellos no comen nada.","Ellas no comen nada.","No comen nada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocino.", answers:["I do not cook.","I don't cook."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I do not cook.", answers:["Yo no cocino.","No cocino."], language:"Spanish"}
	
	]);	
